

# Lourdilene Souza

Software Developer

Technology professional with over 8 years of experience. I have worked with software requirements, programming and consulting on agile methods in the contexts of: education, e-commerce, financial market and marketing. As a Software Developer, I focus on good development practices and delivering value to the client.

### CONTACT

+51 91 99323 3472

🎗 Belém, Pará. Brasil

□ lourdilene.souza@gmail.com

github.com/lourdilene

in linkedin.com/in/lourdilene-souza

## LANGUAGES

Intermediate English

Basic Spanish

### CERTIFICATIONS

PSM | | PSPO | | PBB | KMP | | CLF | MGT 3.0

EDUCATION

2023

#### **ENGLISH EXCHANGE PROGRAM**

Ned College

2015 - 2016

# SPECIALIZATION IN SOFTWARE

**ARCHITECTURE** 

Federal University of Para

2010 - 2015

#### **BACHELOR IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS**

Federal University of Para

EXPERIENCES

2022 - 2023

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Squadra Digital

2021 - 2022

**SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** 

Mobi2Buy

2021 - 2021

**AGILIST** 

Remessa Online

KILLS

HTML / CSS / Javascript

	70%
PHP/Laravel	80%
React	60%
NodeJs	40%

Agile Methods

100%

COURSES

2023

**CURSO.DEV** 

Filipe Deschamps

IN PROGRESS

**BOOTCAMP WEB DEVELOPMENT** 

London App Brewery